[{"answer": "We just looked at the video and we were just surprised of -- because, according to the police report, he sustained injuries, Zimmerman sustained injuries, but when we looked at the video, it was obvious that there were no visible injuries.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What is your reaction to this video?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Piers, this is -- smoking gun.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "How significant is this from a legal point of view?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I believe that George Zimmerman hunted my son like an animal, tried to detain my son.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "I mean, from everything that you have seen, that you've read, that you've heard, what do you believe is the most likely set of circumstances that led to your son being killed?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I absolutely believe that my son would have been arrested.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Sybrina, do you believe if your son had been white and George Zimmerman had been black, that he would have been arrested, George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I would like George Zimmerman arrested immediately.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "What is it, as his mother, that you would like to see happen next?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "I believe that this video is the icing on the cake.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "And do you believe that the video that's emerged tonight should lead to that arrest on the basis that the story that's been put out here in George Zimmerman's defense, that he was being beaten so badly he feared for his life, cannot, as this video would suggest, be true?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "And Sybrina, many believe that you are suffering perhaps even more now since losing your son by the attempt by some people to assassinate his character, to bring out all this stuff about his behavior in school and so on which portrays him in a very damaging light.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "And I just want -- I would just ask him, why did he in fact take my son's life and how does he feel about taking my son's life?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "It bothers me as a mother to hear all of those negative things about my son.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "You know, I'm a parent.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What did you make of what they were saying?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "It's really important, it seems to me, that you have to allow the legal process to take its course.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "But it's just one of those situations where every parent in America, in the world would say, what happened?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "We're bringing back the Wild West.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Doesn't give you the right to pull out a gun and shoot him in the street, is it?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I experienced it for the first time with the Commodores.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "When was the first time that you realized there was racism in America?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I understand.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "You understand?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "The thing about you was you had all the Commodore stuff.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Am I moving you?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "It would be \"Easy\" or \"All Night Long.\"", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Would it really?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "I am a hopeless romantic.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Are you for real a sensitive, romantic, loving type of guy?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "God, you would ask that question.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I do remember.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "You remember that?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Do I have to say it out loud?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "And I should say there was one more.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "And how old was she?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "These are the ones where you go, oh, my God.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "But these are your first loves?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "So you married two of the three people you've been properly in love with?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, you think a little bit more before you say I love you.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "In what sense?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "That you have to throw yourself into it.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "What have you really learned about love?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, mine's easy.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "How do you do it in your marriage?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Oh no, it's perfect.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Do they get on now?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Do you sing at these little tribal meetings?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I will tell you right now, he's not in love yet.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Go on?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "You mean my first love was not enough?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Holy cow.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Who is the biggest romantic sexual singer you've ever deployed?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Has to be.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Has to be?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I think I understand.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "You understand me?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Barry White and Smoky Robinson.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Ever had a Barry White night?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "You understand.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "And candle lit rooms?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I understand.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "You understand?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I understand that.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Do you understand that?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "That was better than mine.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "You like that?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "You are going through what we call panic, because we are perfectionists, or as I say, all artists -- we're egotistical maniacs with inferiority complexes.", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What does the pressure of performance become like when you're going through that deterioration?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "The one that I loved the most was, there's a choice we're making", "docId": "120328pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "I said who sang the best line?", "qSentId": 649}]